you stop?
on birthday I don't know Shut it
search for the first
time Dream it all The sky
to the sky And the sky
comes from the sky The
sky comes from the sky
I can see it Dream it all
Woah
Chess, you're right.
Hey!
Don't just stand around.
Hurry up and go fetch
the medical team now.
Move it.
Don't lose sight of those two.
Slow them down and report
their location to us.
Damn Yamato.
Are you sure you're all right, sir?
You took a pretty major beating yourself
Fair point.
He did clock me pretty good.
Oh my jaw feels a little loose.
That's all that hurts Where
the hell are the medics?
This is an emergency.
Sorry for the wait, sir
That light is super annoying!
Papa! Wow!
Pray for me!
I got a light-threatening boo-boo!
If you're in pain, lie back down.
What's with the attitude?
Shouldn't you be happy I'm not dead?
Ow, get that nasty, Yamato.
How dare that bastard use Commander
Kaido's thunder bagua on me?
Well, I guess she's fine.
More like blunder bad, am I right?
Not like it hurt anyway.
Come on, sis.
Sorry to interrupt.
Both the enemies are currently
stopped in the hall, sir.
Perfect.
Hey!
Papa!
Aren't you forgetting someone?
Where are you taking me?
If you got something to
say, just tell me here.
Don't be hasty.
I promise you this will not take long.
Get out of my way.
Please, just hear me out!
Just say it already!
There are people listening.
We must go somewhere private.
I said no!
I warned ya!
Jungle Palace!
Stubberin, aren't you?
Red Park!
Impressive!
You remind me of someone I once spot.
Damn it all. They're gone.
What's going on?
Where's Yamato?
I'm sorry, sir, but we lost
sight of the both of them.
Surely you all remember
when Kozuki Oden died, yes?
It was the very same day that Oden
Castle went down in a sea of flame.
You know, there is a mystery
lingering from back then.
A group of people
disappeared into thin air.
This little brat sent his
Akazaya Samurai Lockheed.
And where did those fugitives go?
To the future.
To be precise, they traveled
exactly 20 years through time.
Do you get it?
That's why they're here
in the land of Wano
looking the same age
as they did back then.
And who was responsible
for this dangerous magic?
A treacherous witch.
Odin's wretched wife Kozuki Toki.
She thought she could send him here
to kill me, but now I have a son.
We all know that the Kozuki family died
out ages ago, ain't that right, brother?
Damn statement, some real funny stuff!
Hey, hey, Shogun Order Chief, why
don't you come down here with us, bro?
There's no need for you
to get your hands dirty.
Let me at him and I'll
gouge his friggin' eyes out.
How dare you call my mother a witch?
I shall personally make you pay for that.
You dare to challenge me,
you insolent little louse?
I wonder how I should kill you.
A stabbing? A shooting?
Or perhaps I should boil you alive?
Do you have any suggestions, boss?
We have to do something.
They'll kill him.
We must maintain our trust in the Samurai.
It's a delicate situation. Be patient.
Lord Momonosuke, stay strong.
How awful.
We are so close.
The samurai gaze on helplessly as momonosuke
suffers, but maintain their secrecy,
blending in seamlessly at the celebration.
Meanwhile raw submarine
the polar tang reaches its
destination delivering his crew
and several Samurai to the rear
of Onigashima adjust trim
by 38 degrees i'm on it brace
yourselves Get us as close to
the island as you can yes sir
This is a tricky spot We don't want
to get mixed up in all those currents
It's just as bad as above Once we surface
we'll only have one shot I understand
We're counting on you traffy Get us there
Beppo, Chouchou, Penguin, is everyone ready?
Aye aye, Captain!
Aye aye, sir!
Take us to Kaido!
Away we go!
Call systems clear!
We're ready to surface at any time!
Okay, on my call, now!
There's snowing.
Go!
...and shambles.
They're gone now.
Let's pull the doors closed.
Time to resubmerge. Roger!
Ready for rapid descent!
Well, friends, we've made it.
Your ability is quite
extraordinary, Sir Law.
There are two entrances.
I can expect to see Kaido up top.
Hey!
Why do you gotta always
have to be so mean, huh?
I'm just saying you got us into
this mess in the first place.
Hey, wait!
I know that, Yelp!
Ah!
Yagara could've warned me about the drop.
Oh, it's Cat Viper!
Look at you.
You've gotten so much bigger. Huh?
You're alive! Kawamatsu!
Huh?
Ashura!
Is that really you, Yagara?
Indeed it is. Been a while.
Here we go.
Marco!
Did you, Karoo, carry him
here? Mm-hmm. And I'm beat.
Carrying two people ain't easy, you know.
There's two? What?
Wait.
Iso!
It's really you?
My brother!
Kiku, what a fine samurai you've become.
Izo!
I just did not to eat us!
I thought you might never return to Wano.
Right.
Sorry I didn't mention Izo earlier.
Marco said he knew where to find
him, so I went to go pick him up.
Figured we could use him.
Greetings.
You guys haven't changed one bit.
You're too kind.
We'll have time to catch up
on the good old days later.
There is a strange shadow that
I spotted on the way here.
I'd like to go and check it out
It's great to see you Karoo! Be safe.
I'm glad I survived long
enough to see this day!
Kaido's reign will end tonight?
Where the hell is Lin-Lin?
Is she ready to go yet?
Actually, she is!
Big Mom is dressed and
already on her way, sir!
You should have told me that
as soon as you got here.
Uh, whoopsies.
Let's hurry.
Momonosuke's execution will be the perfect
place for my official announcement.
Time to go.
No!
Let's raise a toast to the
death of the Kojo-Keyo!
Commander Call!
The man in the hour is here!
Time to party!
All right.
Listen up everyone,
this execution is depressing as
hell, so I'm gonna liven things up.
It's time for the new Onigashima Project!
You got five minutes?
I thank you.
When I was young, I told my father
I want to become Kozuki Oden.
Huh?
He clobbered me good after that.
I don't see why I gotta hear
your life story right now?
Come on! Get to the point!
I was there 20 years
ago at Odin's execution.
I saw the hour of
legends with my own eyes.
The world will never
see a greater samurai.
And my father and Odichi
are the ones who slayed him.
I can never forgive him.
I was disgusted, of course.
But I was moved as well.
As I cried, I felt a rumbling in my soul.
And then one day, I happened upon
something while I was in Kuri.
It was Kozuki Odin's logbook.
His journal?
Yes.
I live by these passages.
My father and his crew
don't know this item exists.
Odin's grand adventures
and everything important
to him are inscribed
upon these very pages.
Now that the Akazaya Samurai are dead,
someone must carry on Odin's will.
That's why.
I will open this country to the world!
Wait a sec.
Please, allow me to fight alongside you.
Pretty sure you told me you
were Kaido's son a second ago.
Kozuki Oren was a man, wasn't he?
So I chose to become a man too.
I can tell you're strong.
Even when you fought me, it was clear
you were holding back quite a bit.
You really remind me of Ace.
I knew you would show
up sooner or later. Huh?
Although I was a bit concerned,
since we failed to find any
indication that you'd snuck in.
Fortunately for us, it seems
you just got lost on the way.
But even if you're foolish, I know
quite well how persistent you are.
Nya-ha-ha! They're here!
You really called it!
They've been hiding away like scared little
rats ever since the boiling went down.
Conjito, you traitor!
The raid will not be happening today.
Oh, wait.
Is that Izo?
You're back just in time to die.
You made some of our warriors
with their heads removed.
How very artful.
I even tried to make
them look just like you.
It's surprising you've lasted
this long without Odin.
You're powerless without him to lead you.
How quickly you forget
we still have a leader.
Lord Momonosuke will show
us the path to the future!
Where did you take him?
He had better be safe!
Even I cannot say for sure.
He's with Orochi now.
The boy did try to
escape as best he could.
These accursed tunnels
will be the death of me!
Get back here!
I refuse to be averted anymore!
This all ends here!
That was bold.
I can't have you getting away.
If you do, I'll be unable
to fulfill my role.
I had intended to knock
him unconscious cleanly,
but I'm afraid that I must
have overdone it a little bit.
Thankfully, he has some fighting
spirit and was able to cling to life.
Imagine if I'd given the
Shogun his lifeless body.
Lord Momonosuke.
As we speak,
the Shogun is graciously ensuring that
Momonosuke's execution will be a big hit. Ha!
Ha! Ha!
All I have to do is buy them a
little time and it all ends here.
The tale of the Kozuki clan will
officially be nothing but history.
Out of the way, you bastard!
To glory!
Kappa style!
Yachty-kitty.
Flower! Shoot it, kid!
Hold on a second.
What happened to your leg?
You gotta like it.
Two-sword style. That's fancy.
Cool, ain't it?
I'm looking forward to using this
bad boy to plug Kaido full of holes.
How impressive.
Something the matter, Kiku?
Let it out!
There's no need to hold back!
Go on!
Hmm?
Never speak to me again, Kanjuro.
I have heard enough.
Evening shower Kanjuro shall
be remembered as a friend.
But he will exist only in memory.
Prepare thyself.
The wounds this Cotton sears upon thy
flesh persist even into the afterlife.
Like snow that lingers in the spring, it
will torment thy soul for all eternity.
Splendidly saved.
Hey!
Why aren't the video
transponder snails on?
The commander's speech
has already started!
I, Kozuki Oden, have heard much about you.
Now listen well, brother of ace.
A desire to board your pirate ship.
Do you accept?
Oh boy, do you even know how
crazy you sound right now?
Just saying I'm Kozuki
Oden doesn't make it true.
Fine, you're more Oden than me, happy?
Hey, we're Odin!
What the heck does that even mean?
You're free to see the
world just like he was.
I just wish I had that same freedom.
I wanted to travel with Ace
more than anything in the world.
Unfortunately,
I've been imprisoned on this accursed
island since I was eight years old.
Is that what those cuffs are about?
That's correct.
And my father told me that they would explode
if I left the confines of this island.
But to be quite honest, I'm
not sure if he's lying or not.
I mean, what kind of parent
would blow up their own child?
And yet I am stuck here, living in fear.
What if it is true?
Would my father really be that cruel?
I can take him off.
Will me too?
You can?
Listen, do you really want to team
up with us and fight on our side?
You know, joining us means you'd
have to watch me kick your dad's ass.
I would do it myself if I could.
Do you know how many times that man has
raised a hand to me since I was a child?
Whenever I challenged him,
he made sure I paid. Cool.
Come here and I'll get rid of him.
It's not that simple.
These have kept me
trapped here for 20 years.
They aren't ordinary handcuffs, you know.
It's been two years since the
Navy's war against Whitebeard.
And now finally the world has
started to change the seven warlord
system was abolished but not by
coincidence or
some foolish win the
navy must have a new force they're
confident in they think they
have the strength to bring an emperor
of the sea under their control?
Nonsense, but their arrogance has
afforded us a great opportunity.
We shall acquire the ancient weapons and
become the strongest force in the world!
The first step begins right now!
Meet our new ally, Big Mom.
My apologies for the wake.
I heard my name, Polokino.
It had to be big mom
Good to have you back.
Did you miss me?
That's the world's most
powerful hag damn Damn!
She's scary as hell up close!
Traitor Brand's loose!
Nami!
She's gotten a hold of our allies.
So there you are.
About time.
The hell took you so long, Lin-Lin.
Well, I am right here
now, aren't I? Loosen up!
Don't be a stick in the mud.
Today is a momentous occasion.
Kyle and I have big aspirations,
so we formed this a lot.
What's their plan?
We will have to put our differences
aside to make this work.
But if we join sides, then we
can make the impossible possible.
Now, listen up, everybody.
We're gonna show the world
what pirating's really about.
Hold on to your seats.
We're going on a treasure hunt.
Together we're going
to find the One Piece.
No way!
One Piece, did they say the One Piece?
That's my thing, bastards.
People are controlled
by fear and strength.
That's why the ancient weapons will
be an essential part of our operation!
Now I ask you?
Are you ready?
This is the world we seek!
One that's brimming with violence!
Remarkable!
Listen, followers of Uruji, you have
an important choice to make. Yeah?
A choice that will determine your futures.
What is he talking about?
Look at your country the waterfalls that
surround wano make this
land a natural fortress.
One even the navy and the
world government can't
penetrate if we build
more weapon factories.
And force the people of the
flower capital to work in them.
We could transform wano into a
lawless land a pirate paradise.
How dare you how dare
you you talk bastard what
is the meaning of this
madness the flower capital.
Is my territory do you
understand me look at me
kaido perhaps i should
hurry and slaughter this.
Little urchin so you all
show me the reverence i
deserve even the kozuki
clan will fall into line.
Once i parade his corpse
in front of them they
want them to feel the
pain the kuroshumi clan.
Has carried for so long
if anyone is destroying
the land of wano it'll be
me i've already claimed.
It do i make myself
clear kaido i graciously
allowed you to be a guest
here don't forget i'm.
the reason why you were able to
procure all those weapons, damn it!
You need to realize that there is no
land of Wano without me, the Shogun!
Glad you see it my way.
So let's stop stalling.
Take your sword and chop
off that miserable brat.
damn nuisance we don't need him it's done
He had it coming.
Now let me be clear.
The concerns of the Kurozumi mean nothing.
That goes for the Kozuki, too.
Hormo, it's him on the stage. Huh?
I'm coming. Get in there. Be quiet.
They're going to find us.
What the hell was that?
It came from the ceiling.
Your Parasite Lord is dead.
Followers of Orochi.
Now you have five seconds.
Where does your loyalty stand?
Will you choose to die here like he did
or will you conquer the world with me?
We have a lot of preparations to
attend to for the upcoming war.
The choice is clear.
Join my crew.
My pirate empire.
We'll need the extra
manpower for our expeditions.
Tonight we will relocate
our base from this island to
the flower capital and your
country will be no more.
Kaido that rat Wano will be reborn as new
onigashima and the new shogun is my son.
Yamato.
What'd he say?
Shogun?
No way in hell.
Don't you force that on me!
You old piece of shit!
Save it, okay?
We gotta help Momo!
Alright, follow me!
Let's go!